export const WisdomQuizQuestions = [
    {
      question: "What is the definition of wisdom?",
      options: ["Knowledge", "The ability to make sound decisions", "Intelligence", "Experience"],
      correctAnswer: "The ability to make sound decisions"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is often associated with wisdom in Greek mythology?",
      options: ["Zeus", "Athena", "Hercules", "Apollo"],
      correctAnswer: "Athena"
    },
    {
      question: "Which philosopher is known for his teachings on wisdom and virtue?",
      options: ["Socrates", "Plato", "Aristotle", "Confucius"],
      correctAnswer: "Aristotle"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the famous biblical verse about wisdom?",
      options: ["The fear of the Lord is the beginning of wisdom.", "To be wise is to be free.", "Knowledge is power.", "Wisdom is the key to happiness."],
      correctAnswer: "The fear of the Lord is the beginning of wisdom."
    },
    {
      question: "Which animal is often used as a symbol of wisdom?",
      options: ["Owl", "Lion", "Elephant", "Dolphin"],
      correctAnswer: "Owl"
    },
    {
      question: "In which ancient civilization was the goddess of wisdom, Athena, highly revered?",
      options: ["Egyptian", "Roman", "Greek", "Mesopotamian"],
      correctAnswer: "Greek"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the Japanese term for 'wisdom'?",
      options: ["Seishin", "Chie", "Shichi", "Jinsei"],
      correctAnswer: "Chie"
    },
    {
      question: "Who wrote the book 'The Art of War,' which contains many insights on strategy and wisdom?",
      options: ["Confucius", "Sun Tzu", "Laozi", "Machiavelli"],
      correctAnswer: "Sun Tzu"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the name of the famous wise king in the Bible known for his wisdom in judgment?",
      options: ["Solomon", "David", "Moses", "Abraham"],
      correctAnswer: "Solomon"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is not considered one of the three components of wisdom in psychology?",
      options: ["Cognitive", "Reflective", "Affective", "Proactive"],
      correctAnswer: "Proactive"
    }
  ];
  